Guide to the Martin P. Catherwood Library American Labor Union Constitution and Proceedings Project Files 1955-1994
Martin P. Catherwood Library American Labor Union Constitution and Proceedings Project Files
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Martin P. Catherwood Library American Labor Union Constitution and Proceedings Project Files, 1955-1994
/4197
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR); Martin P. Catherwood Library
1 linear ft.
Case files, records (documents).
Kheel Center for Labor- Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Martin P. Catherwood Library; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Library
Form and Genre Terms:
Case files.; Records (documents).
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
CONTAINER LIST
- 1994 UMI (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 1993 UMI (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 1992 UMI (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Copyrighted Documents/Permissions, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 1990 UMI Update (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 1991 UMI Update (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 1989 UMI Update (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 1988 Update (Box 1, Folder 8)
- 1987 Update (Box 1, Folder 9)
- 1986 Upd (Box 1, Folder 10)
- UMI - 1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous = 1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous = 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous = 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Correspondence - Reno, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Page Estimates, 1972-1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Correspondence MCA Project L, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Correspondence MCA Project M-O, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Correspondence MCA Project P-R, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Correspondence MCA Project S-V, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Additional Unions, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Supplement, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- "Lost Material", 1979 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- TRADE/ASSOC, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Trade Assoc., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- ICFTU, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- WFTU. (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Officers Reports, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Misc., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Officers' Reports, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Form - Officers Reports (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Received - AFL-CIO, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Received - CBU (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Received MH-IR (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Received - IU (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Received - MdBJ (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Received - M.I.T. (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Received - MiU (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Received - NYPL (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Received - NjP (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Received - NjR (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Received - DL (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Received - Whi (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Officers Report - Replies from Unions, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Officers Reports - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Union Newspapers, 1980-1991 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Unions, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- UMI Correspondence and Permissions, 1979-1994 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- UMI Listing, 1970-1978 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- American Labor Unions' Constitutions & Proceedings, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 51)